bring fans in today's installment of
在今天的分期付款中吸引粉丝
spring tips we're going
我们要去的春天提示
applications using spring cloud stream
使用Spring Cloud Stream的应用程序
in an earlier video we looked at spring
在之前的视频中，我们看了春天
integration which is a way of building
整合是一种构建方式
event-driven applications in a clean
干净的事件驱动的应用程序
consistent way one thing that we saw in
一致的方式，我们看到的一件事
that spring integration video was that
春天的整合视频是
message channels can be used to connect
消息通道可用于连接
different components the components that
不同的组件
are in the same virtual machine or
在同一个虚拟机中或
indeed components that are distributed
确实是分布的组件
because you can have at the terminus
因为你可以在终点站
ease of these different channels
这些不同渠道的难易程度
adapters and these adapters are one of
适配器，这些适配器是其中之一
the many types of components of spring
Spring 的多种类型
integration shipped with a an adapter is
适配器随附的集成是
meant to transform a Spring Framework
旨在转变一个Spring Framework
message as it transits through a Spring
通过Spring传递的消息
Framework message channel into something
框架消息通道成东西
that can be used in the outside world so
可以在外界使用
we could use a Patrick Kafka we could
我们可以使用Patrick Kafka我们可以
use uki you know we could use them Redis
使用uki，您知道我们可以使用它们Redis
we could use a Twitter we could use
我们可以使用Twitter，我们可以使用
email we could use whatever anything you
电子邮件，我们可以使用任何您使用的东西
can imagine thinking about in terms of
可以想象根据
events or messages can be adapted into a
事件或消息可以改编为
Spring Framework message so I can listen
Spring Framework消息，让我可以听
to messages or events from the outside
来自外部的消息或事件
world I can say whenever a new email
每当有一封新电子邮件时我都可以说
arrives in an IMAP server IMAP idle
到达IMAP服务器IMAP空闲
supporting email service publish a
支持电子邮件服务发布
message or whenever a new message
消息或每当有新消息
arrives on an JMS broker publish a
到达JMS代理发布
message and then I will listen for the
消息，然后我将听
message at the end of the other side of
另一端末尾的消息
that of that channel so we have two
该频道的内容，所以我们有两个
things happening here we've got a
这里发生的事情我们有一个
component that's monitoring the outside
监视外部的组件
world and as soon as it perceives an
世界，一旦它意识到
event it publishes a message into that
事件将消息发布到该事件中
channel and on the other side of course
频道和课程的另一面
we have a component that listens to it
我们有一个监听它的组件
similarly we could have a component that
同样，我们可以有一个组件
publishes messages something that takes
发布消息需要一些东西
a message or generates a message and
一条消息或生成一条消息，并且
then writes it out to an outbound
然后将其写到出站
adapter in this way the message enters
适配器以这种方式进入消息
the channel and then on the other side
通道，然后在另一侧
we have a listener an outbound adapter
我们有一个监听器，一个出站适配器
that translates the message from Spring
转换来自Spring的消息
Framework into something that can be
框架化成可以
used on out in the outside world maybe
用在外面的世界也许
translate the Spring Framework message
翻译Spring Framework消息
into a Twitter message or a file on an
到Twitter消息或
FTP server or whatever write the number
FTP服务器或任何写号码
of things you can talk to we're using
您可以与我们交流的事情
these adapters is myriad and so spring
这些适配器无数，所以春天
negation makes a very very nice basis
否定是非常好的基础
for messaging based integration right
用于基于消息的集成权
this is a the most durable way of
这是最持久的方式
integrating services especially those
整合服务，尤其是那些
separated by a network partition
由网络分区分隔
messaging offers a lot of benefits it's
消息传递有很多好处
temporarily decoupled by
暂时解耦
is to say it doesn't matter if both the
就是说两个
producer and the consumer are alive and
生产者和消费者还活着，
awake and able to respond at the same
醒着并且能够同时回应
time I can write a message to a message
我可以在一条消息中写一条消息的时间
broker and as long as that broker has
经纪人，只要该经纪人有
acknowledged the message and stored it
确认消息并存储
durably then the consumer can come along
持久地，消费者才能走过来
later on and then retroactively Li
以后再追溯李
consume the message so that's one
使用消息，这是一个
benefit of messaging it's also
消息传递的好处
locational decoupling right I don't care
我不在乎位置分离
as a producer of a message or a consumer
作为消息的产生者或消费者
where the message ends up or where it
消息在何处结束或在何处
originates right I just care where about
起源于我只是在乎
where that broker is so I can have as
那位经纪人在哪里，所以我可以
many different clients as I want and
我想要许多不同的客户，
they can live wherever they're wherever
他们可以住在任何地方
they want right they don't have to be in
他们想要正确，他们不必进入
a specific IP or location or anything
特定的IP或位置或其他任何内容
else all I need to worry about is
否则我只需要担心
finding that broker and indeed that
找到那个经纪人，实际上
broker can scale out right so we can
经纪人可以扩大规模，这样我们就可以
have as many instances of that broker as
该经纪人的实例数量与
we need to and to scale it horizontally
我们需要并水平缩放它
so it's very easy to say I want to use
所以说我要用很容易
multicast I'm going to use a ring to
多播，我将使用环
find a broker and then talk to it now by
找到经纪人，然后与之交谈
by working in terms of the message queue
通过在消息队列方面进行工作
we're forced to commoditize our
我们被迫将我们的商品商品化
interactions we're supposed to force to
我们应该强制进行的互动
use a commodity sort of protocol or
使用某种商品协议或
payload rather to talk to each other
有效载荷而不是互相交谈
right so it doesn't matter if one system
对，所以一个系统都没关系
speaks you know Java and then one speaks
会说您知道Java，然后会讲
net and then one speaks C for example
网络然后说一个C
they can all talk so long as they can
他们都可以说话，只要他们可以
talk to that message broker so we've
与该消息经纪人交谈，所以我们已经
also now extended the reach of our of
现在也扩大了我们的
our integration to other different kinds
我们与其他不同种类的整合
of clients this is different for example
例如，这是不同的客户
than what you'd get if you use RPC or
比使用RPC或
something like that that was technology
类似的东西就是技术
specific so we get a lot of benefits by
具体的，所以我们可以从中获得很多好处
using messaging that we don't get with
使用我们无法获得的消息
synchronous RPC kind of interactions
同步RPC交互类型
such as you such as you would have with
像你这样的
a for example EJB right so messaging is
例如EJB权利，因此消息传递是
not a new idea but it happens to be a
这不是一个新主意，但恰好是
really great fit for what we're trying
非常适合我们正在尝试的内容
to do in the micro services world where
在微服务世界里做什么
everything really is just a distributed
一切真的只是分布式的
system a different component and
系统不同的组件和
messaging in particular allows it allows
消息传递特别允许它允许
us to talk to legacy systems systems
我们来谈谈遗留系统
that don't perhaps speak the same
可能讲的不一样
language as the one we're trying to
语言是我们要尝试的一种
speak so integration spring integration
这么说整合 Spring Integration
particular is a great fit for that but
特别适合那个，但是
when we're trying to build modern micro
当我们试图建立现代微型
services we're not trying to integrate
我们不尝试整合的服务
legacy systems right we're building
我们正在构建的旧系统
systems in
系统在
in 2016 or beyond and these components
在2016年或以后，这些要素
are probably going to be able to work in
可能将能够在
working in terms of JSON or XML or
使用JSON或XML或
something sort of modern like that there
那里有点现代
they're probably going to support access
他们可能会支持访问
to modern brokers map modern message
到现代经纪人映射现代信息
queues right so we can take for granted
排队正确，所以我们可以理所当然
that our mut our messaging based micro
我们的mut我们基于消息的微
services today will have access to
今天的服务将可以使用
things like RabbitMQ or Apache Kafka or
例如RabbitMQ或Apache Kafka或
whatever right so in this case we don't
无论如何，在这种情况下，我们不会
really need the full flexibility that
真的需要充分的灵活性
spring innovation gives us it's nice to
春天的创新使我们很高兴
be able to talk to any old system under
能够与任何旧系统通话
the Sun and and be able to talk to it in
太阳，并能够与之对话
terms of messages but that that extra
讯息条款，但那额外
flexibility comes at the cost of having
灵活性是以拥有为代价的
to configure and specify the sort of
配置和指定种类
adapters which again it's nice it's nice
适配器再次很好这很好
that we have those adapters it's nice
我们有那些适配器很好
that we have these components that are
我们有这些组件是
in the sort of crayon box if you will
在蜡笔盒中，如果您愿意
the sort of you know the pallet full of
你那种人知道装满了
colors we have those options but if we
颜色我们有那些选择，但是如果我们
are just going to use rabbitmq or if
只是要使用rabbitmq，或者
we're going to use Apache Kafka for
我们将使用Apache Kafka
example then having to specify that for
然后必须为
every single new communication you know
您知道的每一个新通讯
relay every single new interaction
中继每个新的互动
between components can become tedious
组件之间可能会变得乏味
what I want is the flexibility to work
我想要的是工作的灵活性
in terms of messages I want the
就我想要的消息而言
flexibility to work in terms of the of a
工作的灵活性
message queue and to take advantage of
消息队列并加以利用
all those benefits but I don't want to
所有这些好处，但我不想
have to write so much code that I end up
必须写太多的代码以至于我最终
regretting the the decision to use
遗憾的决定使用
messaging right so if we're willing to
消息传递正确，所以如果我们愿意
take for granted that we're going to use
认为我们将要使用
something modern and commodity like a
一些现代的商品
Apache Kafka RabbitMQ or anything else
Apache Kafka RabbitMQ或其他任何东西
that has for which we can find a binder
我们可以找到一个活页夹
then we can use something called spring
然后我们可以使用所谓的Spring
cloud stream spring cloud stream builds
云流Spring 云流生成
on top of spring integration it has that
在 Spring Integration 的基础上，
it features the same idea of a of a
它具有与a相同的思想
message channel through which messages
消息通过的消息通道
are passed but it makes them it makes a
通过了，但它使他们使
matter of configuration and convention
配置和约定问题
the the wiring of these components so
这些组件的接线
let's go ahead and build a simple
让我们继续构建一个简单的
producer here okay we'll say producer
生产者在这里，好吧，我们说生产者
and the producer will be a web
生产者将是一个网络
application so we have a rest endpoint
应用程序，所以我们有一个休息点
and we're going to send some data in the
我们将在其中发送一些数据
rest endpoint to another service so
将端点休息到另一个服务，以便
we're going to use spring cloud stream
我们将使用 Spring Cloud Stream
we'll use random cue stream processing
我们将使用随机提示流处理
here at startup spring
在 spring boot
and we'll use the actuator because it's
我们将使用执行器，因为
nice to be able to visualize and we can
很高兴能够可视化，我们可以
use integration as well we might we
也可以使用整合
don't need the integration of support
不需要整合支持
here because spring cloud stream and
这里是因为春天的云流和
sprinkled stream RabbitMQ bring in the
洒流RabbitMQ带来了
minimal bits that we need to do the
我们要做的最小位
messaging but it's nice to have the
消息传递，但是拥有
integration component set there if we
如果我们将集成组件设置在那里
want actually we don't really need it
想要实际上我们真的不需要它
for the producer do we we can we can get
对于生产者，我们可以做到吗
a lot we can get by without that that
没有那我们可以得到很多
said that's our producer and then let's
说那是我们的制片人，然后让我们
generate a consumer something that'll
产生消费者的东西会
listen for messages and and then you
听消息，然后你
know accept the data and then do
知道接受数据然后做
something with them so we use h2 we use
和他们在一起，所以我们用h2
JP a will remove the web support we
JP a将删除我们的网络支持
don't really need that anymore and I
我真的不需要了，我
think that'll do that'll be oh we can
认为那会做到的，哦，我们可以
use integration for this we use
为此使用集成
integration to to use the spray notation
集成使用喷雾符号
component model to respond to the
组件模型以响应
incoming message okay so there's that
传入消息好，所以有
now let's build a simple producer now I
现在让我们建立一个简单的制作人
have on my machine right now I have a
现在我的机器上有一个
rabid MQ already running right so I've
疯狂的MQ已经正常运行，所以我已经
got RabbitMQ on my machine as we talked
我们交谈时在我的机器上安装了RabbitMQ
and it's running in the background right
它在后台运行
running on another node which we can get
在另一个我们可以得到的节点上运行
to and what we're going to do is we want
到，而我们要做的就是
to set up an application that produces a
设置产生一个
message whenever somebody calls a rest
每当有人叫休息的消息
endpoint and then we're gonna write that
端点，然后我们要写
message to REM cue and then have it
消息发送到REM提示，然后接收
delivered to our consumer all in terms
全部交付给我们的消费者
of spring cloud streams so again if you
春天的云流再次，如果你
if you haven't seen the spring negation
如果你还没有看到春天的消极情绪
video then it'll be useful to to
视频，这将对
understand what's happening there first
首先了解那里发生了什么
before we get too far into the weeds on
在我们深入杂草之前
this one you don't need to know about
这个你不需要知道的
spray innovation but it's nice to know
喷洒创新，但很高兴知道
about the full power that sort of
关于那种全能
underneath the hood of what we're doing
我们正在做的事情
because you can at any time drop down
因为您可以随时下拉
into spring notation so here we go
变成Spring 符号，所以我们开始
we have an application and we're going
我们有一个应用程序，我们要去
to talk to another service and the
与另一服务交谈
service you know in this case we're just
在这种情况下，您所知道的服务就是
gonna call it consumer because it
称其为消费者，因为它
doesn't particularly have a an
没有特别的
interesting denomination I'm not really
有趣的面额我不是
setting up a particularly plausible
建立一个特别合理的
example here I'm just setting up a basic
这里的示例我只是设置一个基本的
pub/sub or producer-consumer kind of
pub / sub或生产者-消费者类型的
exchange so if we have another service
交流，以便我们提供其他服务
and we want to talk to that service we
我们想和那个服务谈谈
need to have a channel into which we can
需要有一个我们可以进入的渠道
send messages so let's let's first build
发送消息，让我们先构建
a simple wrist controller
一个简单的手腕控制器
okay we'll build the rest controller and
好吧，我们将建立其余的控制器，
now when somebody goes to
现在，当有人去
get mapping we're going to say send a
得到映射，我们要说发送
message actually I guess we can just do
消息实际上我想我们可以做到
a post mapping what about that let's
贴图如何映射，让我们
just do a post mapping and we will just
只是做一个贴图，我们将
accept a message at /and so now when
现在在/等接受消息
public public void publish right here we
public public void在这里发布我们
are publish and what we're going to
发布，我们要去
expect is a JSON structure of type map
Expect是类型映射的JSON结构
okay so look we're going to send a a
好的，所以我们要发送一个
JSON body here and what we want to do is
JSON主体在这里，我们要做的是
we want to write that message whenever
我们想在任何时候写该信息
somebody makes a call to forward slash
有人打电话给正斜线
you know greet let's just call it greet
你知道打招呼就打招呼吧
and we'll pass in a parameter there a
我们将在其中传递参数
path variable there called name so
路径变量那里叫名字所以
whenever somebody sends a a message
每当有人发送消息
that's even better we'll do that we'll
更好的是我们会做到的
just send a message explicitly that it's
只需明确发送一条消息
very simple we don't have to reason or
很简单，我们不必推理或
think about it too much right so
考虑得太对了，所以
whenever somebody sends a whenever
每当有人发送
somebody posts to this endpoint we're
有人发布到此端点
going to send a message to somebody
要发送消息给某人
right we're going to say greeting equals
对，我们要说问候等于
hello name okay so now we want to
你好，名字好，现在我们要
publish that message to a downstream
将该消息发布到下游
service and I could if I had a rest
服务，如果我可以休息的话
service if the downstream service book
服务，如果下游服务手册
rest I could use rest in this case but I
休息我可以在这种情况下使用休息，但是我
can use the rest template and then make
可以使用其余模板，然后制作
a call to that service if I want to but
如果需要，可以致电该服务，但
I don't want to really take that for
我不想真的接受
granted I don't want to take for granted
理所当然的，我不想理所当然
that that service is available all the
该服务在所有时间都可用
time it may well not be available at
时间可能在
this time and if it if it isn't
这次，如果不是
available then I'm going to call a
有空的话我就打电话给
service that isn't there I'm going to
我不打算去的服务
end up dropping State on the floor here
最终将State放到这里
right I need to guarantee that this data
对，我需要保证这些数据
is eventually delivered whenever
最终在任何时候交付
possible so when I'm going to build you
可能，所以当我要建立你
know sort of cognitive systems we need
知道我们需要的某种认知系统
to make sure that these things do the
确保这些事情能够
right thing even in the face of topology
即使面对拓扑也是正确的事情
changes and failures and in this case
变化和失败，在这种情况下
messaging is a better fit so we're going
消息传递更合适，所以我们要
to use spring cloud stream as I said
如我所说，使用 Spring Cloud Stream
before we have spring cloud stream
在我们有春天的云流之前
RabbitMQ on the class path here there
这里的课程路径上有RabbitMQ
are other binders that we could use
是我们可以使用的其他粘合剂
certainly but we've got random queue on
当然，但是我们有随机的队列
my machine it works fine so we'll use
我的机器工作正常，所以我们将使用
that and in order to make this work I
为了使这项工作我
need to find a a connection to this
需要找到一个与此相关的连接
other service
其他服务
so we do this declaratively do this
所以我们声明式地这样做
using an interface so I'm going to call
使用界面，所以我要打电话
this the producer channels interface and
生产者渠道接口和
the name is completely and utterly
这个名字是完全和完全的
arbitrary and what we need to define
任意的，我们需要定义
here is the message channels to which we
这是我们的消息渠道
would like to communicate in this case
在这种情况下想交流
I've only got one channel and the name
我只有一个频道，名字
of the channel in this case because I'm
在这种情况下，因为我
lazy and I don't really have a more
懒惰，我真的没有更多
imaginative name is consumer that is the
想象中的名字是消费者，即
service that we're going to send a
我们将要发送的服务
message to it's our local logical
信息是我们当地的逻辑
perspective this has no bearing on
观点，这与无关
anything in the broker itself this is
经纪人本身的任何东西都是
entirely our perspective of of the
完全是我们对
downstream messaging micro service we
下游消息传递微服务我们
don't care about rabbim queue right now
现在不在乎rabbim队列
we don't care about anything really we
我们真的不在乎我们
just care about what are we doing in the
只是在乎我们在做什么
code right now right this is a channel
现在的代码，这是一个频道
that can send a message out so I'm going
可以发送信息，所以我要去
to annotate this with ad output now we
现在用广告输出对此进行注释
could have multiple definitions here
在这里可能有多个定义
right we in a micro services system you
对，我们在微服务系统中
might have different services that are
可能有不同的服务
sort of a set up and in service to
某种设置和服务于
different parts of the domain parts of
域的不同部分
the business logic right so you might
正确的业务逻辑，因此您可能
have a channel for the you know the
有一个你知道的渠道
customer service and another one for the
客户服务和另一个
order service and another one for the
订购服务，另一项用于
fulfillment service and another one for
履行服务，另一项用于
whatever right different channels for
无论正确的不同渠道
different downstream messaging services
不同的下游消息传递服务
in this case we've only got one and
在这种情况下，我们只有一个
we're going to call it the consumer so
我们将其称为消费者，因此
there was that okay now in order to
现在可以，以便
activate spring cloud stream we say at
激活我们说的 Spring Cloud Stream
enable binding and we tell it about this
启用绑定，我们对此进行介绍
interface definition that we've just
我们刚刚定义的接口
created and now this beam this producer
创建了这个光束，现在这个生产者
channels thing is injectable I can
通道的东西可以注射
inject the producer channels and and use
注入生产者的渠道和使用
it right so I'm going to create a
正确，所以我要创建一个
constructor here I'll create a
在这里的构造函数，我将创建一个
constructor and I'm going to inject the
构造函数，我将注入
producer channels here and remember I'm
制作人频道在这里，请记住我
using Spring Framework 4.3 because I'm
使用Spring Framework 4.3，因为我
using spring boot 1.4 and shrink 4.3 I
使用 spring boot 1.4和收缩4.3我
don't need the ad on a wired annotation
不需要有线注释中的广告
so well I'll leave that off here I'm
好吧，我会把它留在这里
trying to remember to do that and all
试图记住这样做和所有
I'm going to do is I'm going to store
我要做的就是我要存储
the message channel itself right I don't
消息通道本身正确，我不知道
care about the intermediate interface
关心中间接口
but I it's nice to know that I can get
但我很高兴知道我能得到
access to that if I want so I can say
如果需要的话可以访问它，所以我可以说
this Dutch consumer equals channels
荷兰消费者等于渠道
output or that consumer rather
输出或那个消费者
and now I can send a message so this is
现在我可以发送一条消息，所以这是
going to be a Spring Framework message
将成为Spring Framework的信息
this is the very same type of message
这是相同类型的消息
that you use if you use Spring Framework
使用Spring Framework时使用的
support for WebSockets for example -
支持WebSockets-
it's all you know the message object and
这就是您所知道的消息对象，
the message builder and all this the
消息生成器以及所有这些
message channel all that operetta came
消息通道，所有歌剧都来了
from spring integration and Spring
从Spring集成和Spring
Framework for it was merged into the
它的框架已合并到
framework proper right so it's now part
框架的正确权利，现在已经成为一部分
of Spring Framework and it's been around
Spring Framework的诞生
for more than a year so if you have
超过一年，所以如果你有
spring integration and spring framework
Spring 集成和Spring 框架
on clasp and prefer the spring framework
紧扣并喜欢Spring Framework
version of these types right okay so
这些类型的版本好吧，所以
message builder with payload and our
有效负载和我们的消息生成器
payload of course is going to be a
有效载荷当然将是
string there's nothing fancy there I'm
弦，那里没什么好看的
going to then build it right so uh you
然后要正确地建立它，所以你
know just building up a message this is
知道只是建立一个消息，这是
a builder so I could set you know
一个建设者，所以我可以让你知道
headers for example I can add errors and
例如标题，我可以添加错误和
so on I could add an error channel but
所以我可以添加一个错误通道，但是
in this case I just want to you know to
在这种情况下，我只想让您知道
describe the message as quickly as
尽快描述消息
possible so this dot consumer dot send
可能，因此该点消费者点发送
message okay now we've written this
消息好了，现在我们写了这个
entire application in terms of our
就我们而言，整个应用程序
logical use case the logical thing that
逻辑用例
we're trying to do we're trying to send
我们正在尝试做我们正在尝试发送
a message to a rest endpoint and then
一条消息发送到其他端点，然后
send it out to the consumer service we
发送给我们的消费者服务
haven't thus far defined or made
到目前为止尚未定义或制作
concrete what that means what is the
具体是什么意思
consumer service to do this we need to
消费者服务要做到这一点，我们需要
configure we need to configure our
配置我们需要配置我们的
application to talk to random to write
申请交谈随机写
and we do this using convention so
我们使用约定这样做
remember we have spring cloud stream
记得我们有春天的云流
rabbitmq on the class path and the auto
在类路径和自动上的rabbitmq
configuration the spring boot auto
配置spring boot auto
configuration for RabbitMQ has been
RabbitMQ的配置已经
transitively added to the class path so
可传递地添加到类路径中，因此
transitively we're going to have a rabid
传递性地我们将狂犬病
mq connection factory and i could
mq连接工厂，我可以
specify you know the the details for
指定您知道详细信息
that rabid mq connection factory by
那疯狂的mq连接工厂
using any of the well-known properties
使用任何众所周知的属性
all for spring that rabbitmq so spring
春天的一切，那个rabbitmq这样的春天
that Reb mq at addresses and and host
Reb mq在地址和主机上
and the port and the password all of
以及所有的端口和密码
this stuff but the one we have by
这东西，但我们拥有的
default right the one that we have by
默认权，我们拥有的
default here spring that random queue
默认情况下出现随机队列
which connects to localhost and and so
它连接到本地主机等等
on that will work just fine right so
这样就可以了，所以
here's the
这是
okay it's going to connect to 57 56 72
好吧，它将连接到57 56 72
it's already there it's going to connect
它已经在那里要连接
to localhost you can see that here so
到本地主机，您可以在这里看到
that's going to be enough we it's
就足够了
running on my local machine but keep in
在我的本地计算机上运行，​​但保持在
mind that you should and could override
介意您应该并且可以超越
those when you need to what I do need to
那些当你需要我所需要的
do is I need to define the bindings
我需要定义绑定吗
though so I say spring plowed stream
虽然所以我说春耕
bindings dot consumer that destination
绑定点消费者到目的地
equals consumer and this is going to
等于消费者，这将
correspond to a agreed upon rendezvous
对应于约定的集合点
point in the rev MQ broker so remember
指向rev MQ代理，因此请记住
in RabbitMQ RabbitMQ is a is a little
在RabbitMQ RabbitMQ是一个有点
bit different for example than JMS in
例如与JMS在
JMS you have a a deluxe JMS destination
JMS您有一个豪华的JMS目的地
a destination is a logical address if
目的地是逻辑地址，如果
you will in the broker upon which both
您将在两个经纪人之间
the producer and the consumer need to
生产者和消费者需要
agree in random queue there's a little
在随机队列中同意，有一点
bit of an extra indirection there's
还有一些额外的间接
something called an exchange in Rabbid
在拉比德被称为交易所
mq and if you send a message to the
mq，如果您将消息发送到
exchange the the exchange has the
交换交换有
ability to then decide how to route that
然后决定如何路由的能力
message to the appropriate queue so the
消息发送到适当的队列，以便
consumer connects to a queue the
消费者连接到队列
producer connects to the exchange and
生产者连接到交易所，
the in the handoff between the exchange
交换之间的交接
and the queue isn't isn't static it can
并且队列不是不是静态的，它可以
change later right you can change it in
以后更改吧，您可以更改它
the broker itself thus adding the
经纪人本身因此增加了
ability to do extra kind of routing in
能够进行额外的路由选择
fact one of the most handy things you
事实上，您最方便的事情之一
can do there's actually have Reb mq
可以做到实际上有Reb mq
write the message from an exchange to
将消息从交易所写入
another queue which then gets routed to
然后将另一个队列路由到
another queue etc all before it's ever
另一个队列等等，直到永远
delivered to the consumer so you can add
交付给消费者，以便您可以添加
extra steps you can add extra bits of a
额外的步骤，您可以添加一个额外的位
indirection and processing all within
间接和处理都在内部
rather than queue and within AMQP
而不是在AMQP中排队
protocol so we're going to send it to an
协议，因此我们将其发送到
exchange called consumer by convention
习惯上称为消费者的交易所
that'll this will turn into a queue on
那会变成一个队列
the other side we're going to you know
另一边，我们要告诉你
give the same name and it's gonna use a
给相同的名字，它将使用一个
routing key right it's gonna do the
正确路由键，它将做
routing key as well to figure out which
路由键，以找出
queue it should talk to right from the
排队，它应该从右说话
from the exchange alright so there's
来自交易所，所以有
that let's start the application on port
让我们在端口上启动应用程序
8000 there's this as well that'll be
8000也会有这个
enough right that'll be our simple
足够的权利，这将是我们的简单
rabbim queue producer let's start that
rabbim队列生产者让我们开始
up
上
okay there's that that should be enough
好的，那应该足够了
now let's go ahead and look at our
现在让我们继续看一下
consumer the other side of this equation
消费者另一边
right we have to go ahead and build a
对，我们必须继续并建立一个
consumer that's going to take the
消费者将采取
incoming message from the producer from
生产者传入的消息来自
RabbitMQ and then just print it out
RabbitMQ，然后将其打印出来
we'll just acknowledge the receipt of
我们只确认收到
that message right so we'll say consumer
该消息正确，所以我们说消费者
application and in this case we're going
应用程序，在这种情况下，我们要
to do the same thing in Reverse we're
在反向中做同样的事情
going to say interface consumer channels
会说界面消费者渠道
and we're going to say at input this is
我们将在输入中说这是
the reverse right so it's a message that
相反的权利，这是一条信息
will accept delivery it's a channel it
会接受交货，这是一个渠道
accept delivery of incoming messages and
接受传入消息的传递并
in this case the the channel name is
在这种情况下，频道名称为
whatever you want we can actually just
无论您想要什么，我们实际上都可以
call this the producer if you want right
如果需要的话，称其为生产者
so when the message comes in we're going
因此，当消息进入时，我们将
to route it to this channel and we want
路由到这个频道，我们想要
to listen to that message so let's say
听那条消息，所以说
at enable binding and we're going to say
在启用绑定时，我们要说的是
consumer channels class and then we'll
消费者渠道课程，然后我们将
define a spring integration integration
定义一个Spring 集成集成
flow right this is my preferred way I
正确流动，这是我的首选方式
like doing this a lot I like using
喜欢做很多我喜欢使用的
spring negation since I have a lot of
春天的否定，因为我有很多
back on with spring regression but
回到春天回归，但
that's it there's also a component model
就是这样，还有一个组件模型
you can use interpreting code stream
您可以使用解释代码流
right you can use a component model it's
正确的，您可以使用组件模型
been clubbed stream to declaratively you
被流媒体俱乐部以声明方式
know wire a a method invocation to the
知道将线的方法调用到
arrival of a new message so integration
新消息的到来使集成
flows dot from and we're going to take
从中流出点，我们将采取
advantage of our newly continually
我们新不断的优势
created consumer channels right so
这样就建立了消费者渠道
there's this I'm going to say C dot
这就是我要说的C点
input sorry producer handle and what we
输入抱歉的生产者句柄以及我们
want to do is when I want to you know
想做的就是我想知道的时候
just accept the incoming payload and the
只是接受传入的有效载荷和
payload is of type string so I'm going
有效载荷是字符串类型，所以我要去
to say string that class and then we
说那个课，然后我们
have to provide a lambda that will
必须提供一个lambda
accept the headers and the payload and
接受标题和有效载荷
then we'll do something with it and what
那我们就用它做些什么
we're going to do right now is we're
我们现在要做的是
just gonna be turn no then we're going
只是要转不行，那我们要走了
to create the the pipeline the flow
创建管道的流程
there and now we can revisit this now
在那里，现在我们可以现在重新访问
that we know things sort of wired
我们知道东西有点联系
together so all I'm going to do is I'm
在一起，所以我要做的就是
going to log the incoming data right so
即将记录传入的数据，这样
I'll use a a
我会用
logger here or the type and if you saw
记录器在这里或类型，如果您看到
the more the recent video on you know
您最近看过的影片越多
components that you can use inside of
您可以在其中使用的组件
spring framework to make your code more
春天的框架，使您的代码更多
spring aware one of the nice things that
春天意识到一件美好的事
we have there is a an injection point
我们有一个注射点
and that's a very convenient object
这是一个非常方便的对象
there so with that lets us do is we can
在那里，让我们做的是
define loggers like this so injection
这样定义记录器，所以注入
point IP it turn logger dot get logger
指向IP，它将记录器变成点记录器
IP dot get declared type get name right
IP点获取声明的类型获取名称正确
so there's that and now we can inject
这样就可以了，现在我们可以注入
the logger here as well and we can just
记录器也在这里，我们可以
say log or dot info new message payload
说日志或点信息新消息有效负载
ok there we are okay so now there's our
好吧，我们还好，所以现在有我们
consumer it's going to spit up it's
消费者会吐出来的
going to listen for messages that are
将要收听的消息是
coming in on this this input channel and
进入这个输入通道，
as soon as the messages arrive we're
消息一到达我们
going to pass it to this this service
要将其传递给此服务
activator this handle method and then
激活此句柄方法，然后
the handle methods going to simply print
处理方法将简单地打印
out the messages that is arrives ok so
出来的消息就可以了
here we go
开始了
spin that up
旋转起来
okay so this is up and running our other
好的，这已经启动并运行我们的另一个
services on port 8000 to go ahead and
8000端口上的服务继续
send a message to it and we'll say let's
向它发送消息，我们说让我们
see we want to line things up so we can
看到我们想要整理一下东西，以便我们可以
still see what's happening here on the
仍然在这里看到发生了什么
console we're going to say curl minus D
控制台，我们要说curl减去D
that's an mth to be post to localhost
这是要发布到本地主机的方法
8004 session I've already forgotten what
8004会议我已经忘记了什么
the name of the thing was greet name so
东西的名字叫名字，所以
greet world okay so we should see if
问候世界好吧，所以我们应该看看
everything goes to plan hello world okay
一切都按计划进行你好世界好吗
ah it didn't quite work did it we didn't
啊，这还没有完成，我们没有
see the message arrived because we
看到消息到达，因为我们
haven't specified the consumer we didn't
没有指定我们没有指定的消费者
see it we didn't we didn't see it
看到它，我们没有，我们没有看到它
arrived because we haven't specified the
到达是因为我们尚未指定
consumer the the the reverse
消费相反
configuration so spring cloud stream
如此配置， Spring Cloud Stream
bindings dot consumer that destination
绑定点消费者到目的地
equals and what do we say over here for
等于，我们在这里说什么
the agreed-upon rendezvous point equals
商定的集合点等于
well this is the producer the equals
好吧，这就是生产者平等
consumer right so we're going to be upon
消费者权益，因此我们将继续
sending a message to this exchange and
向该交易所发送消息并
pointing this could be you know whatever
指出这可能是你知道什么
actually we could just call this
实际上我们可以称之为
greetings hey we should do that we'll
问候，嘿，我们应该这样做，我们会
call this greetings on both the producer
称这两个生产者的问候
and the consumer there it doesn't really
那里的消费者不是真的
matter right that's just a great
没关系，那太好了
agreed-upon rendezvous point in the
商定的集合点
rebbe MQ broker it doesn't you know that
rebbe MQ经纪人，你不知道吗
can change if I want to this is the Java
可以更改，如果我想要这是Java
channel this is the message channel that
这是消息通道
we created in our Java code so this
我们在Java代码中创建了
can't change this has to match what's in
不能改变它必须匹配里面的东西
the Java code but as long as both
Java代码，但只要两者都
producer and consumer agree upon this
生产者和消费者对此表示同意
and they're both talking to the same
他们都在同一个话题
rabbitmq broker then things will work
rabbitmq经纪人，然后事情会起作用
just fine so this is the consumer and
很好，所以这是消费者，
this will work right this is going to
这将正常工作，这将
work just fine you know we can start the
工作很好，你知道我们可以开始了
application try again now there's the
应用程序再试一次，现在有
message right it says hello world things
正确的消息说你好世界的事情
are fine but but what's going to happen
很好，但是会发生什么
if we set the port to be zero and then
如果我们将端口设置为零，然后
we start this and started a few
我们开始这个，开始一些
different times all right we're going to
不同的时间，好吧，我们要去
start a few different instances I'm
开始几个不同的实例
going to disable a single instance only
将仅禁用单个实例
thing here I'm going to hit apply hit
我要打的东西在这里套用
okay and then I'll restart my consumer
好的，然后我将重新启动我的使用者
create another instance of the consumer
创建使用者的另一个实例
as well so I'll have two of them running
我也要让他们两个跑
at the same time so this one's on fifty
同时，这是五十
one three seven seven here's another one
一三七七这是另一个
running on port well I don't know we'll
在港口运行良好，我不知道我们会
see
看到
so five one four one one and five one
所以五一四有一一和五一
three seven seven so what I'm going to
三七七所以我要去
do now is I'm going to send the same
现在要做的就是我要发送相同的
message I'm going to send another
我要发送另一个消息
message to my producer which is going to
给我的制片人的讯息
then publish the message and we've got
然后发布消息，我们已经
two consumers now what do you suppose
现在有两个消费者你怎么想
will happen hello world there on the
将会在世界上发生你好世界
consumer on one port and hello world
一个港口和世界上的消费者
there again another port that's not
再有一个不是的端口
quite what I think most of us were
我认为我们大多数人都是
probably expecting is it
可能是期望的
we've broadcast the message to two
我们已经将消息广播给两个
different consumers which is fine maybe
不同的消费者，这也许很好
that's fine but if I'm building a system
很好，但是如果我要建立一个系统
where I want to you know deliver the
我想让您知道的地方
message to one and one layer one and
消息传递给一层和一层
only one consumer then this is probably
只有一个消费者，那么这可能是
not what I want and instead of
不是我想要的，而不是
load-balancing by adding more consumers
通过增加更多消费者来实现负载平衡
to divide the work I've duplicated the
划分我复制的作品
work I've broadcast the work and that's
我已经广播了作品，那是
that's not what I want so what I want to
那不是我想要的，所以我想要的
do in my consumer is is a define a group
在我的消费者中做的是一个定义组
okay so I can call this whatever I want
好吧，我可以随便叫这个
this the name here the group name is
这个名字在这里组名是
completely arbitrary this is a consumer
完全任意，这是一个消费者
group and in spring cloud stream
组和 Spring Cloud Stream
parlance that means that if I have one
说法是，如果我有一个
or more consumers in the same group only
或同一组中有更多消费者
one instance in that group will get any
该组中的一个实例将获得任何
one given message so it's exclusive to
一个给定的消息，因此它是专用于
among the among them the members of that
其中的成员
group the message will be delivered
组邮件将被传递
exclusively to one node so I'm going to
专用于一个节点，所以我要
call this the greetings group and we're
称呼为问候组，我们
gonna go ahead and restart this instance
要继续并重新启动此实例
here and then this instance whoops on
在这里，然后这个实例大声疾呼
that one there okay there's this and
那里的一个人那里是这个
we'll restart this one so now I've
我们将重新启动这个，所以现在我已经
restarted both of them with this new
用这个新的重启了他们两个
configuration right
配置权
now two everything goes to plan we
现在两个事情都按计划进行了
should see it this is 51 469 this is 51
应该看到它是51469这是51
472 we should see the message delivered
472我们应该看到传递的消息
to one and only one consumer right we
我们只有一个消费者
should see it on the canto of just one
应该只在一个Canto上看到它
node so let's try again here we go okay
节点，所以让我们再试一次，我们可以
it didn't get delivered to this one
它没有送到这个
hopefully got delivered to this one
希望能送到这个
there it is hello world so now our
那里是世界，所以现在我们
consumer group has done what we expected
消费者群体已经完成了我们的预期
it to let's see if I make another call
看看我是否再打一个电话
may be the load bounced for us yep the
可能是我们的负荷反弹了
the second one got it right so we're
第二个没错，所以我们
effectively load balancing the work now
现在有效地负载平衡工作
where this is called a work stealing
这被称为偷工
right we can have as many consumers as
对，我们可以拥有尽可能多的消费者
we need another way to another pattern
我们需要另一种方式
another name for this pattern is called
这种模式的另一个名字叫做
the the aggressive consumer right so
侵略性的消费者权利
what's happening is we're taking as much
发生的事情是我们正在采取尽可能多的措施
work as we can from the queue but if we
从队列中尽力而为，但如果我们
have more consumers and we're able to
有更多的消费者，我们能够
divide our ability to handle that work
划分我们处理这项工作的能力
which is ideal if you're for example
例如，这是理想的选择
using Cloud Foundry okay so this is
使用Cloud Foundry好吧，这是
we've looked at what happens if we have
我们研究了如果有
one or more instances of the consumer
消费者的一个或多个实例
what happens if we have zero what
如果我们为零会发生什么
happens then how do we well you know how
发生了，那么我们怎么知道你知道如何
do we make sure that if we deliver a
我们是否确保如果我们提供了
message that the the messages is
消息是消息
processed eventually even if there is no
即使没有
consumer by default this is not the
消费者默认情况下不是
behavior that we'll have so if we have
我们将拥有的行为
if we have zero instances of the service
如果我们有零个服务实例
available then that message will sit
可用，那么该消息将坐下
dormant on the broker it's still there
在经纪人处休眠，它仍然在那里
it's been acknowledged by the broker but
它已被经纪人承认，但
we don't have anything to take delivery
我们没有什么要收货的
of that message in to do something with
该消息的目的是为了
it so what we need to do now is to make
所以我们现在要做的是
our our subscription durable right so
我们的订阅持久权是这样
we're going to take this here and we're
我们要在这里带走，
going to say producer that durable sub
要说生产者那耐用的子
script chin equals true okay so now
下巴脚本等于真的好吧，所以现在
we've got three attributes here for this
为此，我们具有三个属性
producer channel that we've just
我们刚刚制作的制作人频道
described in our definition here
在我们的定义中描述
producer is this channel now I'm going
制片人是我现在要去的这个频道
to say that the subscription is durable
说订阅是持久的
so if we kill this and kill this so both
所以如果我们杀了这个然后杀了这个
of them are gone I have no instance here
他们中的人走了，我在这里没有实例
goodbye and I have no instance here and
再见，我在这里没有实例
now I'm going to send another message
现在我要再发送一条消息
I'll say hello world durable world right
我会说你好世界持久世界吧
we should see this now delivered on
我们现在应该看到
start up I'm going to send the message
启动，我要发送消息
oh whoops we'll send the message I'm
哦，糟糕，我们将发送邮件给我
going to say you know again for example
比如说你再次知道
so we should now have two messages that
所以我们现在应该有两个消息
are sent to the broker but not yet
已发送给经纪人但尚未
confirmed not yet delivered so we're
确认尚未交付，所以我们
going to start up an instance of this of
将要启动一个这样的实例
this consumer and we should see it retro
这个消费者，我们应该看到它复古
actively consume the messages that have
积极消费具有
been delivered to RabbitMQ on the
已在以下位置交付给RabbitMQ
console here right there's Hello durable
控制台在这里，你好耐用
and hello again so it worked right we've
再次问好，所以它工作正常，我们已经
we successfully sent a message from the
我们已成功从发出了一条消息
consumer from the producer rather to the
从生产者到生产者的消费者
broker and then to the consumer but
经纪人，然后到消费者，但
we've also taken care of uh you know
我们也照顾了你
we've looked at how to do
我们已经研究了如何做
publish/subscribe as well as
发布/订阅以及
point-to-point kind of messaging and
点对点的消息传递和
we've looked at how to build systems
我们研究了如何构建系统
that do the right thing in the face of
面对
service outages and failures after all
毕竟服务中断和故障
that is one of the big benefits of using
这是使用的最大好处之一
a message broker is the ability to store
消息代理是存储的能力
and then forward those messages that
然后转发那些消息，
gives us the ability to take then take
让我们有能力接受然后采取
down a service and still guarantee that
停止服务并仍然保证
everything gets processed eventually
一切最终都会得到处理
right we're not able to take down our
对，我们无法撤下我们的
consumer if we need to and upgrade it
消费者是否需要升级
and you know deploy a new version
而且您知道部署新版本
whatever without losing the data it's
在不丢失数据的情况下
eventually consistent we will eventually
最终一致，我们最终
process the data and the world will
处理数据，世界将
converge upon a a well known state
汇聚到一个众所周知的国家
eventually so this has been a brief look
最终，这是一个简短的外观
at spring cloud stream now spring cloud
在春天的云流现在春天的云
stream builds a punch spring integration
流构建冲压Spring 集成
in a later video we're going to look at
在后面的视频中，我们将看
something called spring cloud dataflow
所谓的Spring Cloud Dataflow
which makes it dead simple to then
这样就很简单了
compose or to sort of Koya graph lots of
组成或排序的Koya图很多
small messaging based micro services
基于小型消息传递的微服务
like this in support of stream
像这样支持流
processing right the the sort of
正确地处理
perpetuation of messages through a
通过以下方式使消息永久存在
series of messaging based services to
一系列基于消息的服务
arrive at a more complex result sort of
得出更复杂的结果
like the pipes and filters model that
例如管道和过滤器模型
you're you may be filled with if you've
你就是，如果你已经
used bash in the UNIX command line shell
在UNIX命令行shell中使用了bash
alright thanks very much for watching
好，非常感谢您的收看
and I'll see you next time
下次见
you
您